Boss.
Well,
Wen Yanhui is here, Boss.
Got it.
[Dearest: Episode 17]
Grandpa, what brings you here?
Today is Alex’s birthday.
As an elder,
I have to do something to celebrate.
After all, he helped Wen Group.
I prepared a gift in advance.
But it seems that
the birthday boy is not here anymore.
I knew it.
No one knows that Jiang Yu is back.
But it's okay.
Well, I suppose this birthday gift
is a memorial gift now.
I'll take this gift.
When he comes back in a few days,
I'll ask him to personally thank you.
By the way,
after the board meeting,
I'll have a big gift for Grandpa too.
Consider it your retirement gift.
Okay, let's wait and see.
Something is definitely off
about this statue.
I've thought so
ever since it showed up here.
Wen Yanhui is clearly
up to something today.
Let's see what's wrong with this statue.
Hao.
Smash it.
Uncle Long, iced Americano.
It's been a while
since I've had something this pure.
And you managed to make this from here?
I work with pharmaceuticals,
so the principle is basically the same.
I pretended to be sick a while back
and stockpiled some cold medicine.
I extracted some of the compounds from it
and was able to make this.
Just a little something I picked up,
Uncle Long.
I know your situation.
You want to get out so badly?
Uncle Long, as long as you let me out,
I'm willing to do anything for you.
Uncle Long.
With your old connections, your influence,
and my skills,
I'll make you rise again
and reclaim your position.
And maybe reach even higher.
Do you like it, lady?
You turned me on,
so you'd better take responsibility.
Lady.
You really know how to play.
Is it exciting?
Help! Rape!
Someone raped me!
Help!
Lady! Lady!
Rape! Rape!
I was raped in Cloudsea.
That's too much.
He thought I'm pretty,
dragged me into the toilet
and raped me.
Madam, please calm down.
Cloudsea will
take responsibility for this.
We will make sure you're compensated.
Compensate?
How are you going to compensate me?
How?
Do you know what makes me happy?
Murder!
Wen Jianan from Cloudsea killed someone.
What's wrong with Wen Jianan?
She's late for such an important occasion.
I heard Cloudsea is having some trouble.
Dear shareholders,
according to the company's bylaws,
any candidate who is 30 minutes late
it will be deemed
to have withdrawn voluntarily.
There are less than five minutes left.
I'm afraid candidate Wen Jianan
won't be able to make it.
Police have preliminarily confirmed
[Suspected body
found inside plaster statue in Cloudsea]
that what was found in the bag
was not a human body,
but a clothing mannequin.
The case is still under investigation.
Grandpa, I'm here.
Five minutes left. I'm not late, am I?
Why are you...
The statue Grandpa sent to Cloudsea
really had a secret hidden inside.
Dear shareholders,
I'm here today
not only to run for chairman,
but also to expose something.
Candidate Wen Yanhui
attempted to sabotage the election
by killing someone,
hiding the body, and trying to frame me.
Murder?
What evidence do you have?
The person you killed
and tried to frame me for killing
was my biological mother,
Wen Yan.
Didn't the old chairman die long ago?
Yes.
Chairman Wen Yan is Wen Jianan's mother?
How do you explain that?
Nonsense!
Everyone here knows
Wen Yan died 20 years ago.
Wen Yanhui.
No.
I should call you Chen Hui now.
Years ago, just before the board election,
you deliberately staged
Wen Yan death's as a car accident.
In reality, you kept her locked away
in a dark basement for 20 years.
20 years?
This is how
you stole the Wen Group from her.
And now, just to take it all for yourself,
you killed her again.
Wen Jianan, you are really good
at making up stories.
Do you have proof that I killed Wen Yan?
You are framing me.
This is slander, you know?
Fine.
Then I'll show everyone the evidence.
This...
Mom.
Mom!
Chen Hui.
Everything you took from her,
I'm taking back now.